<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<kdramas>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">A Gentleman's Dignity</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2012</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>This drama will tell the story of four men in their forties as they go through love, breakup, success and failure. </about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Boys Over Flowers</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama, School</genre>
        <year>2009</year>
        <episodes>25</episodes>
        <about>Jan Di, the Heroine, is the poor but bright girl who has a strong sense of justice and full of vitality. She transfers to an exclusive high school where only the rich go. In there, she encounters with the four rich and quirky boys and experiences love and friendship</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Goblin</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Melodrama, Supernatural</genre>
        <year>2016</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Goblin, who once was an unbeatable General in ancient times and died tragically, possesses an immortal life and hopes to end the torture by finding a human bride who can pull out the hidden sword in front of his chest. Having searched for the bride for 900 years, one day, he met Ji Eun Tak who can summon him and claims that she is his bride.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Gunman In Joseon</title>
        <genre>Historical, Suspense, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>22</episodes>
        <about>In the time of enlightenment of 19th-century Joseon. It stars a hero who is the son of Joseon’s greatest swordsman. He loses his father and his younger sister gets sold as a slave, after which he trades sword for gun as he embarks on his revenge mission, and in so doing the drama will "depict the pain and courage of the young people of the era."</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Maids</title>
        <genre>Historical, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Set in the Joseon Period, Kook In-Yeob is the only child in a noble family. She is famous for her beauyl and stylish appearance. Due to an incident, her status falls to the lower class. As she struggles through her misfortune, she becomes stronger.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Moon Embracing The Sun</title>
        <genre>Historical, Romance, Fantasy, Political</genre>
        <year>2012</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Set in the Joseon dynasty, two brothers find themselves falling in love with a female shaman, who does not remember her noble past.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Obstetrics and Gynecology Doctors</title>
        <genre>Romance, Medical</genre>
        <year>2010</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>The drama depicts the difficult decisions and moving human stories that take place daily in the OB-GYN department, focusing in particular on Seo Hye Young, a talented and determined obstetrician who has just transferred from the prestigious Seoul base to the branch hospital. Her straightforward manner of handling her professional life is in contrast with her love life, which is marred by her relationship with a married man. This becomes even more entangled when she meets Lee Sang Shik, the chief of NICU, and her long-time friend Wang Jae Suk also shows his interest.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">She Was Pretty</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2015</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Kim Hye Jin was a very pretty girl from a rich family. After her family's publishing company went bankrupt, she experienced hardships then lost her beauty too. Ji Seong Jun was an unattractive boy with low self-esteem, but grows up as a handsome and successful editor.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Sungkyunkwan Scandal</title>
        <genre>Historical, Comedy, Romance</genre>
        <year>2010</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Kim Yun Hee is a smart, responsible young woman with an independent drive. Since her father passed away she has worked to support her family, but also managed to do well in her studies. When her younger brother's illness worsens and their family is in danger of being evicted from their house for lack of money. In her desperation to support him, Kim Yoon Hee decides to take the men's only nationalexam under her younger brother's name and disguises herself as a boy. On the day of the exam, Kim Yun Hee meets Lee Seon Joon and becomes friends. Lee Seon Joon comes from a privileged background and also possesses good looks. He is also arrogant. They both pass the national exam and she has to share a room together with him at Sungkyunkwan University, while hiding her true nature. There, she becomes friends with the playboy Goo Yong Ha and rebellious Moon Jae Shin.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">The Emperor: Owner Of The Mask</title>
        <genre>Historical, Romance, Drama, Political</genre>
        <year>2017</year>
        <episodes>40</episodes>
        <about>In the 1700's, Crown Prince Lee Sun fights against Pyunsoo hwe, an organization that has accumulated power and wealth through privatizing water all over Joseon. He becomes a hope for the people who suffer. Ga-Eun is the woman Crown Prince Lee Sun loves and she helps him grow as a ruler.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">The King's Face</title>
        <genre>Action, Historical, Romance, Drama, Political</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>23</episodes>
        <about>Drama series follows the life of Prince Gwang Hae. Even though he is the child of a concubine, he becomes the crown prince. For the next 16 years, until he becomes the King, Prince Gwang Hae suffers through dethronement and death threats. Using physiognomy as a weapon, he is able to become the King.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Twenty Again</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2015</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>38-year-old Ha No Ra dreamt of becoming a dancer in her high school years, but met her husband Kim Woo Chul when she was 19. After having a child, she focused on taking care of her family and had to give up her dreams. In hopes of becoming a proud wife and mother to her college professor husband and her son Min Soo, she strives to enter college and ends up getting accepted into the same college as her son.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Winter Sonata</title>
        <genre>Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2002</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Joon Sang moves to a new high school in search of his biological father. Yu Jin and Sang Hyuk are close childhood friends, although Sang Hyuk wants to be more than a friend, Yu Jin sees him as a brother. On a trip together with other high school mates, Oh Chelin, Jin Suk and Yong Kuk, Yu Jin is saved after an accident by Joon Sang. They become close and she opensup his cold heart. However, circumstances and fate dictate that their love will never be. He abruptly disappears from their lives. Ten years later, he returns, but as someone else and without memory of his past.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Another Miss Oh</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Melodrama, Supernatural</genre>
        <year>2016</year>
        <episodes>18</episodes>
        <about>There are two women named Oh Hae Yeong, who were classmates in high school, getting all mixed up in each other’s lives because they share the same name. The problem is that they not only share the name, but they also have the same occupation, which is probably the bigger issue. They both come to work for the same large catering company, but one is a team leader while the other issimply an assistant manager. Then there’s also a man in their lives, who has the ability to see into the future.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Marriage, Not Dating</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama, Family</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Wealthy plastic surgeon Gong Ki Tae is a successful and happy bachelor who does not want to find himself a wife. He believes that his life is perfectly planned, and being single is the only option he accept. However, his family is badgering him to marry. In an effort to get his parents off his back about the constant string of blind dates and marriage prospects, Ki Tae purposely brings Joo JangMi home to meet his parents posing as his girlfriend, certain that they'll never approve of her.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">My Love from Another Star</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Melodrama, Supernatural</genre>
        <year>2013</year>
        <episodes>21</episodes>
        <about>Do Min Joon is an alien who landed on Earth 400 years ago during the Joseon Dynasty period. He possesses a near perfect appearance and enhanced physical abilities involving his vision, hearing and speed. Later, he discovers that he has three months left on Earth. And that is when he meets Cheon Song Yi, the biggest Hallyu star in Korea.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">City Hunter</title>
        <genre>Action, Suspense, Mystery, Crime, Romance, Political</genre>
        <year>2011</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Lee Yoon Sung is a talented MIT-graduate who works on the international communications team in the Blue House. He plans revenge on five politicians who caused his father's death with his surrogate father Lee Jin Pyo and eventually becomes a "City Hunter". </about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Secret Garden</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Melodrama, Supernatural</genre>
        <year>2010</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>The drama tells the story of Kim Joo Won, an arrogant and eccentric CEO who maintains the image of seeming perfection, and Gil Ra Im, a poor and humble stuntwoman whose beauty and body are the object of envy amongst top actresses. Their accidental meeting, when Joo Won mistakes Ra Im for actress Park Chae Rin, marks the beginning of a tense, bickering relationship, through which Joo Won tries to hide agrowing attraction to Ra Im that both confuses and disturbs him. To complicate matters further, a strange sequence of events results in them swapping bodies.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Coffee Prince</title>
        <genre>Friendship, Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2007</year>
        <episodes>17</episodes>
        <about>A tomboy is mistaken for a young man, but maintains the deception for the sake of employment. The situation is complicated when her male boss begins to develop feelings for this "boy".</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Descendants of the Sun</title>
        <genre>Action, Military, Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2016</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>This story tells of doctors stationed in the fictional war zone of Urk (Uruk), and follows the love story that develops between a surgeon, Kang Mo Yeon' and a special forces officer, Yoo Shi Jin, both elite in their respective fields. The story will track both their personal and professional struggles while exploring issues about the value of life.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Healer</title>
        <genre>Action, Mystery, Comedy, Drama, Romance</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Seo Jung Hoo is so-called "errand boy". For a relevant price he may complete any task, only if it's not connected with murder. Under Healer's mask he had run foul of some organizations that now strive to catch him, however no one knows who he really is. He can count on older woman's help, genius hacker responsible for the technical part of their job. One of his tasks is closely connected toone girl, Chae Yeong Shin, second rate tabloid reporter. She starts to have an interest about Healer when he tries to get close to her, which results in the discovery of their common past.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Reply 1997</title>
        <genre>Friendship, School, Comedy, Romance</genre>
        <year>2012</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Set in the 1990's, the drama centers around a female high school student Shi Won, who idolizes boyband H.O.T and her 5 high school friends in Busan. As the timeline moves back and forth between their past as 18-year-old high schoolers in 1997 and their present as 33-year-olds at their high school reunion dinner in 2012, where one couple will announce that they're getting married.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">It's Okay, That's Love</title>
        <genre>Friendship, Psychological, Comedy, Romance, Medical, Drama</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Jang Jae Yeol is a famous mystery novelist and popular radio DJ with a prickly personality. After meeting psychiatrist Ji Hae Soo when they both serve on a talk show panel delving into the criminal mind, they instantly rub each other the wrong way. But when Jae Yeol’s girlfriend plagiarizes his work, forcing him to lie low until the media storm blows over and he can prove his innocence, he unexpectedly becomesHae Soo’s roommate. Jae Yeol moves into a home that he owns that is being rented by Hae Soo; Jo Dong Min, another psychiatrist and Hae Soo’s senior colleague; and Park Soo Kwang, a young man with Tourette syndrome. As Jae Yeol and Hae Soo’s personalities clash, they help each other heal from their own deep-rooted emotional scars.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Rooftop Prince</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Supernatural, Drama, Historical</genre>
        <year>2012</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Crown Prince Yi Gak finds that he has been transported from the Chosun Dynasty to modern-day Seoul. He meets Hong Se Na, who bears a striking resemblance to his dead wife, and is determined to solve the 300-year-old mystery of her death. With his own resemblance to the CEO’s grandson at the company where Se Na works, Gak assumes the identity of the young man to stay close to her. Can theCrown Prince navigate a modern corporation to find clues to his own time period?</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Strong Woman Do Bong Soon</title>
        <genre>Action, Comedy, Romance, Thriller, Supernatural, Drama</genre>
        <year>2017</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Do Bong Soon is a woman with superhuman strength. With her strength she gets hired as the bodyguard of the spoiled CEO of the gaming company Ainsoft, Ahn Min Hyuk. Min Hyuk is being threatened by an unknown enemy, and is determined to solve the problem himself out of his distaste and distrust of the police. In Guk Doo is a policeman and Bong Soon’s crush since childhood. When series of kidnappingsoccur in Bong Soon’s small, quiet neighborhood Dobong-dong, their little community is thrown into chaos. Combined with the job of protecting her boss’s life, Bong Soon’s already unusual life has gone wild. However, she must be careful; if she missuses her strength, she could lose it forever.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Faith</title>
        <genre>Action, Historical, Medical, Fantasy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2012</year>
        <episodes>24</episodes>
        <about>A 21st-century plastic surgeon Eun Soo gets kidnapped and brought 700 years in the past for her healing powers. Goryeo era bodyguard to the king General Choi Yeong is smart but a little naive, he almost never smiles. He faces conflicts with the female doctor Eun Soo, but soon feels attracted to her.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Emergency Couple</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Medical, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>21</episodes>
        <about>Jin-Hee led a satisfying life as a dietitian. She then met medical school student Chang-Min. Despite his wealthy family's strong opposition, Jin-Hee and Chang-Min decided to get married. Chang-Min's family is full of doctors. Chang-Min though gave up his medical internship and began working as a pharmaceutical salesman. Their marriage life was not happy. Chang-Min's family looked down on Jin-Hee and even Chang-Min seemed to change. Chang-Min began to think terribly ofJin-Hee and they finally divorced. After their divorce, Jin-Hee became a medical student and now works as an intern. Chang-Min also graduated from medical school and begins to work as an intern. One day, they meet in the emergency room for a hospital where they will both work together.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Fated To Love You</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2014</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>A chaebol heir and a "post-it" girl are forced to marry after their one-night stand results in an unexpected pregnancy.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Hello Monster</title>
        <genre>Thriller, Mystery, Psychological, Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2015</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Genius profiler Lee Hyun, returns home to Korea after something from a case he’s been sent triggers a memory he thought he’d lost forever. Unbeknownst to him, one of his team members, Detective Cha Ji-an, has been investigating him for some time. She is aware that his father was murdered and his brother disappeared under mysterious circumstances involving a criminal named Lee Joon Young -- whom they both want found and incarcerated.Each seeks to unravel the other, unaware that they’ve been drawn into a dangerous game of cat and mouse by a master player and that both truth and evil are closer and far more twisted than they think.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Gu Family Book</title>
        <genre>Historical, Fantasy, Supernatural, Romance, Martial Arts</genre>
        <year>2013</year>
        <episodes>24</episodes>
        <about>Choi Kang Chi, born as a half-human-half-mythical-creature, goes through struggles in order to live more like a human than anyone else despite not being able to become human. He is the son of Gu Wol Ryung, the guardian spirit of Jiri Mountain, and Yoon Seo Hwa, an ordinary human. Choi Kang Chi later was raised by adopted family. He grows up as an outspoken character who's full of curiosity and one day,he realizes that he's a half-human-half-beast through a certain incident and starts living his second life. While going through the struggles, he met Dam Yeo Wool who is a master of martial arts and archery at a young age and then, they both fall in love with each other.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Arang and the Magistrate</title>
        <genre>Suspense, Historical, Supernatural, Comedy, Romance</genre>
        <year>2012</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>Arang and the Magistrate tells the story of a cynical and not so friendly government official named Eun Oh who wanders the whole nation to look for his mother who disappeared because of his mistake. Eun Oh has the ability of seeing ghosts, so he's used to be bothered by many kind of ghosts. As a result he isn’t afraid of ghosts anymore. Then Eun On meets a virgin ghost named Arang. Before she became a ghost, Arang was a beautiful girl who was murdered. Arang asks Eun Oh to seek vengeance for her death and Eun Oh tries to appease her request.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">My Lovely Sam Soon</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama</genre>
        <year>2005</year>
        <episodes>16</episodes>
        <about>Kim Sam Soon is a baker who has a talent in making pastries and cakes. On Christmas Eve, she caught her boyfriend, Min Hyun Woo, cheating on her and breaks up. On that same night, she accidentally went into the men's restroom and met Hyun Jin Hun. By sheer coincidence, Jin Hun needs a baker for his restaurant Bon Appetit and Sam Soon is unemployed. Sam Soon is hired as the restaurant's chief baker and the two fight like cat and dog.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Love In The Moonlight</title>
        <genre>Historical, Comedy, Romance, Melodrama, Political</genre>
        <year>2016</year>
        <episodes>18</episodes>
        <about>Hong Ra On disguises herself as a man and counsels men on dating. Due to a love letter she wrote for a client, she meets Crown Prince Hyo Myeong. Ra On is unaware that he is the Crown Prince and Hyo Myeong is unaware that Ra On is a woman. The Crown Prince becomes interested in Ra On. His eunuchs become aware of this and attempt to get Ra On to become one of them.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Hwarang</title>
        <genre>Friendship, Historical, Comedy, Romance</genre>
        <year>2016</year>
        <episodes>20</episodes>
        <about>The names of just a few Hwarangs are recorded in history. Not many people these days truly know about Hwarangs. How did they start? How did beautiful looking young men become at the center of unifying old Korea's Three Kingdoms? To these countless questions, we look forward to finding the answers. Let's imagine how life must have been for young people of Silla back in the 6th century. Let us tell you a story about their friendships and love.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Suspicious Partner</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Law, Romance</genre>
        <year>2017</year>
        <episodes>40</episodes>
        <about>Noh Ji Wook is a unique prosecutor. He is handsome, hard-headed and intelligent who strives hard to be successful. He is the perfect example of what a prosecutor should be. Later, he becomes a lawyer. Eun Bong Hee is a prosecutor trainee. Once a former taekwondo instructor, she trained to become a lawyer. She is confident and strong, but naive. She is assigned to work under Ji Wook. They work together on a mysterious case involving a sly psychopath murderer. As they're working as a team, they develop affection between them.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">I'm Not A Robot</title>
        <genre>Comedy, Romance, Drama, Sci-Fi</genre>
        <year>2017</year>
        <episodes>32</episodes>
        <about>The story of a man who lives an isolated life due to a severe allergy to other people but meets and falls in love with a woman who pretends to be a robot.</about>
    </kdrama>
    <kdrama>
        <title lang="en">Empress Ki</title>
        <genre>Historical, Romance, Drama, Political</genre>
        <year>2013</year>
        <episodes>51</episodes>
        <about>The series revolves around Ki Seung Nyang, a Goryeo-born woman who ascends to power despite the restrictions of the era's class system and later marries Ta Hwan to become an empress of the Yuan dynasty, instead of her first love, Wang Yu. The series depicts her loves and political ambitions.</about>
    </kdrama>
</kdramas>